dooxi.com 2012-12-19

# Privacy Policy and Disclaimer | Dooxi.Com

We respect the privacy of all of users and is committed to protecting such privacy in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy explains the treatment of your personally identifiable information collected in connection with your activities on or related to the website referencing this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy also explains how you can ask questions and make suggestions about our privacy practices and review and update your personal information. We urge you to read this Privacy Policy carefully and to check back periodically as this Privacy Policy may change from time to time.

**INFORMATION COLLECTED**

In the course of operating the website, we may collect two types of information about our users: Personal Information and Non-Personal Information.

“Personal Information” is personally identifiable information, such as your name, and email address. Personal Information is collected by us when you choose to provide it to us when registering, or choose to receive a newsletter. In addition, if you choose to contact any of our customer service representatives, we may keep a record of that correspondence so that we may fully address the subject matter. We may also receive Personal Information from our business partners and other third parties, provided that such third parties confirm to us that you have permitted them to share such information.

“Non-Personal Information” is information of an anonymous nature, such as an Internet Protocol Address (IP Address) , the domain used to access the website, and the type and version of browser or operating system being used. Aggregate information, such as demographic statistics of our users (e.g. average age or geographical allocation of our users), number of visitors and average time spent on a website, is also considered Non-Personal Information. Non-Personal Information is collected or derived by us in the course of operating the website. For example, our Web servers may automatically collect Non-Personal Information which is provided through your browser or stored on a Cookie when you choose to visit the website. Non-Personal Information is used by the website as described here .

**USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

****Personal Information may be used by us for the following purposes:  
Providing you with the information you have requested from us. We may from time to time use your Personal Information to contact you about changes, enhancements or similar notices related to the website;

**LINKS TO OTHER SITES AND ADVERTISEMENTS**

This website may contain links to other websites and services. While we try to link only to sites and services that share our high standards and respect for privacy, please understand that we are not responsible for the content of, or the privacy practices employed by, other companies or websites.

**SECURITY**

The security of your Personal Information is important to us. We take technical, contractual, administrative, and physical security steps to protect Personal Information that you provide to us. We instruct our employees with access to your Personal Information that it is to be used only in adherence with the principles set forth in this Privacy Policy and the laws applicable to each specific business.

**CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

This website may from time to time change its Privacy Policy. Changes will be effective when notice of such change is posted on the site. Please check this Privacy Policy regularly for updates by checking the date of “Effective Date” at the top of this document.
